Excuse me?
¿Disculpe?
Excuse me, sir?
¿Disculpe, señor?
Oh, come on.
Oh, por favor.
Do you have a moment, sir?
¿Tiene un momento, señor?
I'm kind of in the middle of something here. Yes? Thank you.
Estoy algo ocupado por aquí. ¿Sí? Gracias.
I've come a long way for you, Franck.
No fué fácil encontrarte, Franck.
My name is Victor.
Soy Victor.
Hi.
Hola.
And you are....
Y tú eres...
You are Franck.
Eres Franck.
You are so much more than just a sheep, aren't you?
Tu eres más que una simple oveja. ¿No es cierto?
Oh yeah? How would you know?
¿Ah sí? Y usted qué sabrá.
Look at you. You're an adventurer, Franck.
Mírate. ¡Eres un aventurero, Franck!
Just like me, you're... a lone wolf.
Como yo, tú eres... un lobo solitario.
Tell me, does one choose to be alone?
Dime. ¿Acaso uno elige estar sólo?
No, one doesn't.
No, nadie lo hace.
One doesn’t even choose to be a wolf.
Uno ni siquiera elige ser un lobo.
Or does one?
¿O sí?
Well, mister... err... Hector.
Bueno, señor... err... Hector.
Victor. Victor.
Victor. Victor.
I don’t know what you’re on about but I'm just a sheep minding its own business.
No sé qué pensará usted pero yo soy sólo una oveja viviendo su vida.
And I suggest you do the same.
Y le sugiero que haga lo mismo.
No. No no no, Franck. Wait wait wait.
No. No no no, Franck. Espera, espera, espera.
No. This is not... the way.
No. Ésta no es... la manera.
Just give me one minute of your precious time.
Sólo pido un minuto de tu preciado tiempo.
Precious time? Hehehe.
¿Preciado tiempo? Je je je.
Yeah just give me one minute.
Sí, sólo un minuto.
You would have one more minute, wouldn't you?
Tienes un minuto, ¿no?
Okay half. Half a minute.
Bueno, medio. Medio minuto.
I knew it.
Lo sabía. Lo sabía.
You will not regret this.
No te arrepentirás.
The adventures you will have.
Las aventuras que tendrás.
All the lives you've ever wanted.
Todas las vidas que siempre quisiste.
All you’ve been missing.
Todo lo que te has perdido.
Here. This is... the best product we have... in store.
Toma. Es el mejor... electrodoméstico... que tenemos.
Variable spin speed, excellent tumble performance...
Múltiples velocidades, el mejor centrifugado...
...in one... handy... device. Squeaky clean.
...en un... sólo... producto. ¡Impecable!
Well this... this better be good.
Bueno... más vale que sea bueno.
Took me ages to tie that rope.
Fué difícil atar esa soga.
With my fucking hooves.
Con mis malditas pezuñas.
No more need for hooves.
No habrá más pezuñas.
No more sheepy business.
No más problemas ovinos.
Ho! Time flies.
¡Oh! El tiempo vuela.
Wait wait wait wait wait wait.
Espera espera espera.
How does this thing work?
¿Y esto cómo funciona?
I mean, how do I make it work?
¿Cómo lo enciendo?
No you don't.
No hace falta.
I just turned it on for you.
Acabo de encenderlo por tí.
When can I go?
¿Cuándo empiezo?
Where can I go?
¿Adónde voy?
We will pick you up. Don't worry, just stay here.
Nosotros te buscaremos. No te preocupes, quédate aquí.
In this exact place.
En éste preciso lugar.
Don't move. Just wait.
No te muevas. Sólo espera.
That's it?
¿Eso es todo?
Hey!
¡Hey!
Wait, mister!
Espere. ¡Señor!
Eh, Casper!
Eh. ¡Casper!
Hector whatever!
¡Hector, como sea!